The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
During his time off, Asta paid a visit to Hajj Village.
On the way, he unexpectedly met up with Yuno,
who was also returning home.
When they arrived, they learned that the villagers
had already heard the rumors regarding Asta's
alleged involvement with a devil.
I saw you in the newspaper.
Oh yeah, I can explain.
That article isn't correct at all.
Asta isn't being controlled by a devil.
He's doing everything he can to defeat devils.
That's the truth behind it.
In reality, no one in the village had doubted Asta for a second.
On the contrary, they were deeply proud of him and Yuno
for becoming magic knight and protecting Hajj.
Though their visit was brief, it was quite pleasant.
Our story's not over yet.
It's only the beginning, Asta.
Let's protect everyone.
And keep moving forward.
Thank you so much for turning out what I have now.
Let's protect everyone's life.
I know you're there.
Guanji says goodbye Punch Seaертв.
He's in blood.
And the nature of Trien,
Parents and может tattoos.
Oh, Israel
Yeah, yeah
абсолютно
and
it
me
the
Now I'm叫ぶ your喉が降り切れるほど
未来は自分で切り開くんだ
せとめとなく溢れ出る情熱のまま
さあ歩き出そう
To live my dream
It'll make your head spin!
Somebody's fired up first thing in the morning
I don't think your little rivalry is our top priority right now
Better make sure you get all your nutrients
Wow, thanks!
Hi-ya! Now I'm ready!
We need to start building our skills
Then we can hit that devil with everything we've got
In that case, everybody eat up right now
Thanks Charmy, this is delicious
Oh look you guys, Magna got a cake to the face
Oh who's making that racket?
Don't you know this hideout is the home of the Black Bulls
Aka the future best magic knight squad in the-
Ah ha!
Whoa why does this moment feel so familiar?
Hey it's the scary lady
Captain Merrilyuna
You should do something about that weak door of yours
Oh hello there, what can we do for you today ma'am?
I don't say yummy, but that's fine
Everyone in this room is coming with me immediately
I have nothing but bad feelings about this!
You could have always saw me finish eating my food!
Yay! This'll be fun!
With all due respect, ma'am, can you just kidnap a whole squad this way?
Could you maybe at least tell us where we're going?
Quiet! You'll see shortly.
I'm confused.
Wait, what just happened? One minute we're at the hideout and now we're surrounded by molten lava?
Oh, how exciting is this?
I can feel the calories burning away and I've got nothing to replace them with!
Oh, right. I guess this place can throw you for a loop if you haven't been here before.
It's a strong magic region. Yultim Volcano.
Yultim, huh?
Excuse me, ma'am, but why exactly did you bring us here?
For your training, of course!
Oh, right.
Leo! Captain Feigalion!
It's good to see my rival again.
You must have been pretty busy lately dealing with the elf attack and a devil.
That's right. I heard that you were on the front lines fighting with the Crimson Lion Kings.
Wait, is it just me or have you gotten taller?
Yeah, but that's not the only thing different about me. I've been improving my skills as a mage, too.
Oh, really? Well, my muscles are bigger, so I'll still beat you!
Hello, Black Bulls. Can you spare a moment?
Huh?
I happen to be the vice-captain of the Crimson Lion Kings. My name is Randall Lufthair.
During the last battle, the three of us had our bodies taken over by elves.
Even though we weren't in control of our actions, we're exceedingly sorry for betraying our land.
Don't apologize. None of us are to blame for what happened except for the devil who messed with everybody's heads.
And I hear the devil in the spade kingdom is an even greater threat.
Our squads must be strong to protect our nation.
But in order to prove Asta's innocence, we'll each have to improve ourselves individually as well.
Precisely, so just like before, my own squad, the Crimson Lion Kings, will be training alongside the others I invited.
Right!
We weren't so much invited as abducted, but sure, whatever.
Here we go! Let's race to the top so we can hit that sweet hot spring!
Hold it!
There'll be no climbing this time. Instead, I'm going to have you venture below.
To the underground cave!
Huh?
There's a cave?
But what's down there?
This place is a strong magic region.
Because deep beneath the surface lies a great mana heat source.
Rocks that are soaked in that mana become lava and burst upward.
Which means, the further you descend, the more intense the heat source's influence will become.
If your mana skin falters, your body will be exposed to the extreme heat
and you will be reduced to ashes.
However, you'll be pleased to hear that the hot spring awaiting you in the deepest part of the cave is even more satisfying than the one at the peak.
Now then! Does that motivate you?
Hot spring.
Yeah, I don't like this! I'd be a lot more comfortable in a sweet region overflowing with honey, not lava!
Believe me, you're not ready for that!
It's real?
Okay, someone gonna tell me what mana skin means?
It's a defensive technique. To put it simply, it's a way of enhancing your physical abilities through mana.
It's magic in its perfect state.
Simply wrap your magic around yourself and it will form a protective shield of mana to cover your body.
Hang on, you can't expect us to do it right off the bat!
Then I guess you'll just be incinerated.
Oh, thanks!
Since you were brought here unexpectedly, I suppose it's only fair that I allow you to use this magic item.
What is it?
Something that will make it a little easier for you all to call upon your mana skin.
But it's only a supplement.
So if you lose control of your magic, then it will no longer be effective.
Oh, yeah! It's time to get started!
I've got flame magic, so I'm pretty sure a volcano will be a sitch.
Now I'm gonna fight fire with fire and blaze a trail to the finish line!
That's what you think, Leo! I'll fight as hard as I can to make it to the goal before you!
Wait a sec, genius. How are you planning to do that if you can't use mana skin?
That anti-magic technique takes a lot out of you and doesn't last long.
If it wears off, you're toast!
I know!
In the past, I was able to switch over to my dark form by using the power flowing through the sword and into my body.
I didn't really have any control of it at the time, but luckily, I can handle it a little bit better now.
I'm gonna concentrate and focus my powers. That way I won't get sucked in by the magic inside the cave!
Not bad!
He surrounded himself with anti-magic.
Right. This should do it!
Hey! That's pretty impressive! Now I'm really ready to take you on!
Yeah, I'm ready too! I don't have time to be scared! I gotta figure out how to use mana skin so I don't get barbecued!
Aw, Magna's a chicken!
Come here and say that again, smart guy!
Poor little scaredy cat!
Shut your freakin' mouth!
Mana skin... I should be able to put it on using my Valkyrie armor.
Hmph.
I see you're all prepared. Remember, you are the esteemed magic knights who serve this kingdom.
One thing should burn far hotter than the mana inside this volcano. Your desire to pass this test!
Yeah!
I'm gonna get there first!
No me!
Hot spring.
I won't be beaten either.
Better hurry! You don't wanna get left behind, do ya?
You itch!
No time to waste!
Right!
Sneaky sneak.
Charmy, you're leaving?
Sheesh!
This place obviously doesn't have any restaurants, so there's no reason for me to stay! A girl's gotta eat, you know?
Yeah, but...
I won't stop you.
Huh?
Scorching hot mana isn't the only danger in this cave. You'll also face fearsome creatures that have adapted to those conditions. If you lack the desire to improve, then flee.
That's right. I want to get stronger so I can help my friends. I can't turn back.
So the creatures that live here, are they yummy?
More so than you can fathom.
I'm sold! Let's go down there and taste those undiscovered trees marinated in extra spicy mana!
Wait for me!
I'm eager to see how many of them will be able to make their way to the goal.
Hmph. It'd be too boring if it were just a simple race.
Hmph.
When I decided that this cave would be their training ground, I had much more in mind.
I'm gonna be the first one there, so you might as well give up already!
Hold it, you slowpump!
Don't you move!
Ow, it's so hot!
The deeper we go, the thicker that crazy mana gets, and the more it starts to wear out our bodies.
Oh man, I'm so tired and dizzy.
All I can do is yell really loud!
I won't give up!
You can't beat me, Asta!
Hey Nero, what was the point of you coming here?
Well, there's a hot spring.
So it's a vacation for you!
They're so noisy!
It's making it harder to concentrate on my magic.
Just calm down, Noelle.
If you get mad, you'll lose control.
On second thought, they both died today.
Pick up the pace!
Asta and Leo are about to leave us behind!
Let's show them what the Crimson Lion Kings are made of!
Sir!
That's the spirit!
The heat from this mana is no joke.
Magic item or not, if I slip up, I'll burn to death.
Whoops! Sorry, Magma!
You did that on purpose, brat!
That's it!
You are so dead!
Also, are you sure this is even a shortcut to the goal?
Shouldn't we be going down?
I'm not too sure, but it doesn't really matter
because apparently there's a super tough opponent up here somewhere
and I'm just itching to fight!
What? And you weren't planning on telling me?
We don't have time for a side mission, you dumbass!
Whoever it is, this aura is crazy powerful!
How am I supposed to resist?
Hi-yah!
Now come to Mama!
It's so hot!
My mana's draining faster than expected!
Listen, Charmy, it's not safe for us to be down here for very much longer!
Huh? But we need to eat the tasty mystery creatures so we can replenish our magic power!
I don't know, I haven't seen you catch a single thing. I'm starting to think there's nothing here.
That can't be right! I sense them! They have to be nearby!
I get it now! The monsters must be hiding because they're afraid of something!
It's probably you.
No!
It's so powerful, Charmy! Come on! You have to let go of the net now!
I'm not letting my snack get away!
Some things are more important than food!
I can't hold on anymore!
No, please!
You okay?
That was a close call!
Look, Magna, you saved us!
What's the matter with you, you selfish jerk?!
How dare you stand in the way of all this unknown deliciousness?!
I think that giant spider over there wanted to eat you too, Charmy!
And if I'm not mistaken, that's the tough opponent that we've been looking for!
What do you mean, we?!
Oh, man! No fair, I lost sight of it!
You want me to starve?!
I see. That spider must be what the other monsters were trying to hide from before.
I'll eat a good meal or else I'm trying!
I'm not done yet.
You sounded pretty out of breath there, Asta.
You look like you might pass out.
I'm close to my limit, but at least my rival is in the same boat.
I'll be the first one to the hot spring!
In your dreams!
Reinforcement magic! Leg strength boost!
Move!
Whoa, so fast!
The mana's so intense here, and my water magic is the worst possible match for it. This is way harder than I thought.
I'm royalty just like she is, so why are we at different levels?! I can't let her beat me!
Don't get all cocky, Noel! We're right behind you!
I'm gonna be the next Wizard King, so there's no way I can let myself lose!
Asta, I remember when I met you.
Now you better listen to me! I'm gonna get results like no one has before!
I'll do whatever it takes to become the Wizard King and prove you wrong!
Even though you were nothing but a commoner with no magic, when you told us about your dreams, I felt something deep in my heart.
Since then, we fought together, trained together, and competed against each other to grow as mages.
I tried to join the Royal Knights to get revenge for what the Eye of the Midnight Sun did to my brother.
But I wasn't strong enough. You were.
Either way, it's not the end for me. I'll train harder, surpass you both. Watch me!
Wow, Leopold!
I'll get revenge for Captain Foygolion. You don't have to worry about that.
I still carry that frustration. And to this day, I've continued to try my hardest.
I will catch up to you!
I'm not at the goal yet. I'm running out of steam.
Hey! Wait for me!
I'm royalty, remember? People wait for me, not the other way around.
Noelle!
Swim drops! No, that can't be right. I must be seeing things.
Here I come!
Ow!
Breathe, Noelle. Okay, now try looking one more time.
There's no need to rush. Let's just take a break and go for a swim.
Why in the ocean?
Whoa, I need to get a grip.
We're in an underground cave below a volcano. This isn't a day at the beach.
You okay?
Geez, what the heck was that for?
Hey, where'd you go? Come back!
That stupid Asta. If he didn't want to be attacked, then he shouldn't have spoken to me.
Huh?
Amana seems to be calmer in here. I wonder why.
Asta?
Did something just...
Aaaaaaah!!
Aaaaaaahhh!!!!
Uh... metrics
Aaaaaahhhh!!!
Hi! Glad your' reok. Where did this ugly thing come from?
« дома»
Oh, no!
Water creation magic!
See dragon's floor!
No!
Eat this!
Flame magic!
Viral flame!
Leopold!
Are you okay?
You can stand, yes?
Yeah.
You three handled yourselves fairly well against that beast.
I suppose we can mark this training session a success.
Wait, what?
You see, that mutant bug recently showed up and started eating all the other creatures that live here.
I was hoping to teach it a lesson.
But it seems to be able to sense foes that are too strong for it.
So it never shows itself in my presence.
That's why I decided to bring all of you down here instead.
And of course it tried to devour you just as I'd intended.
So you planned this whole thing?!
You knew it was down here?
Why didn't you say something?
Silence!
The battlefield is rife with surprises.
Besides that, we're preparing to challenge a powerful devil.
How will you do it?
How will you win if you can't squash a bug?
She's right.
I wasn't thinking about it that way.
We should have done better.
That's what I would say.
Except this spider is more dangerous than a typical mutant.
I sense man-made mana in it.
Mana that it definitely didn't possess at birth.
Quite strange.
That unusual mana must be what allowed it to conceal itself from you.
And if it's an elaborate form of camouflage that even I couldn't see through,
then it may be a curse.
Where does that door lead to?
Ah, a dungeon!
This ought to be interesting.
That I'll be interested in.
When it's suppose to have a good kullani level,
It's not a bad idea right now.
I got scared from one time distbourg doctrine.
That'll give rise to the past.
Me, it has battled.
I ga confirm the truth.
Oh, I'll beた.
With that turn around right away.
I don't need to be afraid of the wrong path
There's no wrong path
There's no one in there
I don't have a mistake
Don't finish it
I'll hold my heart
I'm not one here
No matter what it takes
I swear that I'm gonna catch up and surpass you
Number one
Please Captain Yummy
If you don't come out of there soon
I think I'm gonna go pee on the floor
Later
Hey!
You didn't surpass me
You just caught in line
Number two
Alright, let's chow down
Hmm?
Where's your food?
Ha!
I just surpassed you in eating
Well, you didn't need anything
And number three
Nah, I'll surpass that and skip to a hundred
No, ten thousand
It makes no sense
A dungeon, huh?
Move over, Asta
Cause I'm about to conquer it
Before you even get a chance
Black Clover, page 133
The Lion Awakens continued
I'm gonna shake the whole underground
With my mighty roar